{
    "subject": "resource/Pooja_Sharma",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Pooja Sharma is an Indian television actress and model. She is most popular for her role as Draupadi in the mythological TV show 'Mahabharat'.",
    "human_readable": "Pooja Sharma's comment is that she is an Indian television actress and model, and she is most popular for her role as Draupadi in the mythological TV show 'Mahabharat'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7458716630935669,
            "question": "Which character did Pooja Sharma play in 'Mahabharat'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.734911322593689,
            "question": "What can you infer about Pooja Sharma's career based on her comment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7061323523521423,
            "question": "What TV show is Pooja Sharma most known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6236217617988586,
            "question": "How might fans describe Pooja Sharma's performance in 'Mahabharat'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5150766372680664,
            "question": "What country is Pooja Sharma from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5090159773826599,
            "question": "What type of show is 'Mahabharat'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4969439208507538,
            "question": "What profession does Pooja Sharma have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49434980750083923,
            "question": "What is one of Pooja Sharma's notable achievements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47991153597831726,
            "question": "Is Pooja Sharma a known personality in the entertainment industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4350658059120178,
            "question": "Besides acting, what other profession does Pooja Sharma have?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pooja Sharma's comment is that she is an Indian television actress and model, and she is most popular for her role as Draupadi in the mythological TV show 'Mahabharat'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8352_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Pooja Sharma a known personality in the entertainment industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8352_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is one of Pooja Sharma's notable achievements?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8352_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What profession does Pooja Sharma have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8352_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8352_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8352_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8352_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8352_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8352_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8352_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8352_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8352_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8352_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8352_68.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information provided, I can confirm that the statement about Pooja Sharma is indeed supported by the documents.\n\nHere's the response in the requested JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Pooja Sharma being an Indian television actress and model. They also mention her famous role as Draupadi in Star Plus\u2019s Mahabharat, which supports the statement given in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}